timesharelifestyle.com 2010-06-24

# Privacy Policy | Call 1-800-616-1966

## Privacy Policy

This privacy notice discloses the most current privacy practices for www.TimeshareLifestyle.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.  
2\. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.  
3\. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.  
4\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.  
5\. Other notices about this web site.

Information Collection, Use, and Sharing  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We also share your personal information with companies that perform services on our behalf, such as companies providing timeshare related legal services and travel agents. Our service providers and strategic partners are bound by contract to use the personal information we share with them only for the limited purposes for which we provide it to them and to take reasonable measures to protect the confidentiality, integrity and security of your personal information. They may not use or share your personal information in a manner that would be inconsistent with our promises to you, and they must comply with all applicable privacy and data protection laws.

We may share or transfer your personal information to unrelated third parties, if disclosure is required to comply with a law, regulatory requirement, court order, or a subpoena; to cooperate with law enforcement or other governmental investigations; to protect your and our legal rights, property and safety, our employees, agents, other guests.

If you choose not to receive any promotional communications from us or our partners, you must notify us in writing at the email address or mailing address provided at the bottom of this page. Upon receipt of your written request we will not send you purely promotional messages and will not share your personal information with other companies. We may still contact you for customer research or administrative purposes, such as confirming a reservation or transaction you’ve made.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

Your Access to and Control Over Information  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us in writing via the email or mailing address given at the bottom of this page:  
\- See what data we have about you, if any.  
\- Change/correct any data we have about you.  
\- Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

Security  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.  
This website is monitored by Hacker Safe. Our hosting provider and data is in a secure environment.  
Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

Other  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.  
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to make changes to this Policy at any time.

We will notify you of any material changes to this Policy by posting a notice on at the top of the revised Privacy Policy page for at least 30 days after the new effective date to let you know what has changed. It is your responsibility to check our website periodically for changes to this Policy.  
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via one of the methods below.

Phone: 1.800.616.1966  
Fax: 727.209.1422  
Email: [help@timesharelifestyle.com](mailto:help@timesharelifestyle.com)  
Mail: 9675 4th Street North | St. Petersburg, FL | 33702
